<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="global" table="sn_aia_version">
    <sn_aia_version action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <condition/>
        <instructions>The agent operates through a precise, automated sequence, functioning continuously without human intervention until the final case is created, structured, and routed.

# Step 1: Ingestion &amp; Monitoring
Action: The agent actively monitors the designated incoming support channel, focusing specifically on email-originated interactions to initiate the triage process.
Input: The agent ingests the new email interaction record, which contains both the body text and any attachments.

# Step 2: Attachment Processing &amp; Summarization
Action: The agent accesses and processes all attached documents to synthesize the core issue. It generates a concise, actionable summary that eliminates the need for a human analyst to review every file.

## Tools Used: The agent utilizes the following sequence: 
--&gt; Retrieve attachments of an interaction record, 
--&gt; Summarise attachments on the interaction record 
--&gt; Get attachment summarization results.

Output: Consolidated summary of all attachments on the interaction record.

# Step 3: Interaction Record Enrichment
Action: The output from the summarization (Step 2) is used to update the original interaction record with the new attachment summaries, creating a complete data package for the next step.

Output: The interaction record is updated, now containing the generated attachment summaries.

# Step 4: Specialized Case Classification
Context: The agent leverages a tailored Capital Markets skill and model trained on historical operational data, knowledge and key business reference data (e.g., Trade Exceptions, Settlements, Regulatory Filing issues, etc.).

Action: The agent analyzes the extracted data and the synthesized summary to accurately determine and classify the precise request type (e.g., classifying "Trade Issue" as "Failed Settlement - T+2 Equities").

Key Outputs Determined: This step determines the necessary metadata for the new case, including:
--&gt;Case Table (e.g., sn_bom_treasury_wire_service)
--&gt; Business Activity Name (e.g., Unmatched Trade), 
--&gt; Business Activity ID (e.g. f565708f2fec7a50b14f861cbfa4e359)
--&gt; Summary 
--&gt; Description.

Step 5: Seamless Case Generation
Actions:
--&gt; Case Creation: The agent instantly creates a new support case in the target system.
--&gt; Data Population: All relevant fields are pre-populated using the classification outputs from the previous steps. 
---&gt; Case Table and Business Activity ID must match the predefined return format exactly.
---&gt; The Summary and Description contains the agent-generated actionable summary.</instructions>
        <state>published</state>
        <sys_class_name>sn_aia_version</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-11-07 23:30:57</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>global</sys_domain>
        <sys_id>c842f5ca938576d00f91fce79503d67a</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>2</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>V1</sys_name>
        <sys_overrides/>
        <sys_package display_value="Pete's Email Engagement Toolkit" source="x_snc_pab_ee_tkit">01900de693acba502e03fde1a903d651</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Pete's Email Engagement Toolkit">01900de693acba502e03fde1a903d651</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sn_aia_version_c842f5ca938576d00f91fce79503d67a</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-11-09 16:02:41</sys_updated_on>
        <target_id>9510f586938576d00f91fce79503d6a4</target_id>
        <target_table>sn_aia_agent</target_table>
        <version_name>V1</version_name>
        <version_number>1</version_number>
    </sn_aia_version>
</record_update>
